A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "ISOFLURANE: Isoflurane (Forane): a new inhalation anesthetic", 23:112, 1981 December 25 (Box 541, Folder 1138-1142)
- "SWEETENERS, ARTIFICIAL: Aspartame and other sweeteners", 24:1, 1982 January 8 (Box 541, Folder 1143-1144, Box 542, Folder 1145-1151, Box 543, Folder 1152)
- "SUCRALFATE: Sucralfate - a new drug for duodenal ulcer", 24:2, 1982 January 8 (Box 543, Folder 1153-1160)
- "SARALASIN: Saralasin fir diagnosis of renovascular hypertension", 24:3, 1982 January 8 (Box 544, Folder 1161-1167)
- "TEMAZEPAM: Temazepam (Restoril) - another benzodiazepine for insomnia", 24:16, 1982 February 5 (Box 544, Folder 1168-1171, Box 545, Folder 1172-1175)
- "TUBERCULOSIS (CHEMOTERAPY): Drugs for Tuburculosis", 24:17, 1982 February 19 (Box 545, Folder 1176-1178, Box 546, Folder 1179-1186)
- "SEXUALLY TRANSMITTED DISEASES: Treatment of sexually transmitted diseases", 24:29, 1982 March 19 (Box 547, Folder 1187-1194, Box 548, Folder 1195-1196)
- "TIMOLOL: Timolol for hypertension", 24:44, 1982 April 30 (Box 548, Folder 1197-1202)
- "TRANZODONE: Tranzodone (Desyrel) a new nontricyclic antidepressant", 24:47, 1982 May 14 (Box 549, Folder 1203-1208)
- "VARICELLA-ZOSTER IMMUNE GOLBULIN: Varicella-Zoster immune golbulin", 24:51 and Correction, 24:74, 1982 May-August (Box 549, Folder 1209-1212, Box 550, Folder 1213)
- "VERAPAMIL: Oral verapamil for angina pectoris", 24:56, 1982 June 11 (Box 550, Folder 1214-1220)
- "ZYDERM: Zyderm collagen implant", 24:69, 1982 July 23 (Box 551, Folder 1221-1225)
- "POTASSIUM: Micro-K potassium supplement", 24:71, 1982 August 6 (Box 551, Folder 1226-1231)
- "PSORIASIS: Phototherapy for psoriasis", 24:72, 1982 August 6 (Box 552, Folder 1232-1239, Box 553, Folder 1240)
- "SNAKEBITE: Treatment of snakebite in the USA", 24:87, 1982 October 1 (Box 553, Folder 1241-1247)
- "STAPHYLOCOCCAL INFECTIONS: Treatment of methicillin-resistant staphylococcus", 24:107, 1982 December 10 (Box 554, Folder 1248-1252)
- "PRAZIQUANTEL: Praziquantel - a new antiparasitic drug", 24:108, 1982 December 10 (Box 554, Folder 1253-1258)
- "RANITIDINE (ZANTAC): Ranitidine (Zantac)", 24:111, 1982 December 24 (Box 555, Folder 1259-1265)
- "CANCER CHEMOTHERAPY: Cancer chemotherapy", 25:1, 1983 January 7 (Box 556, Folder 1266-1273)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Treatment of hypothermia", 25:9, 1983 January 21 (Box 557, Folder 1274-1281)
- "GUANABENZ: Guanabenz (Wytensin) a new antihypertensive drug", 25:11, 1983 January 21 (Box 558, Folder 1282-1288)
- "PINDOLOL: Pindolol" and "Dosage of Pindolol", 25:13 and 26:102, 1984 November 9; 1983 February 4 (Box 558, Folder 1289-1292, Box 559, Folder 1293-1299)
- "NONSTEROIDAL ANTI-INFLAMMATORY DRUGS: Toxicity of Nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs", 25:15, 1983 Feb. 4 (Box 560, Folder 1300-1307, Box 561, Folder 1308)
- "DILTIAZEM: Diltiazem for angina pectoris", 25:17, 1983 February 18 (Box 561, Folder 1309-1316)
- "NUTRITION & DIET (INFANTS): Oral rehydration solutions", 25:19, 1983 February 18 (Box 562, Folder 1317-1321)
- "ARRHYTHMIAS: Treatment of cardiac arrhytmias", 25:21, 1983 March 4 (Box 562, Folder 1322-1325, Box 563, Folder 1326-1331)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Cefoperazone sodium (Cefodid)", 25:29, 1983 March 18 (Box 563, Folder 1332, Box 564, Folder 1333-1340)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUGS FOR): Malathion for treatment of head lice", 25:30, 1983 March 18 (Box 565, Folder 1341-1349)
- "TRIAZOLAM: Triazolam - a new benzodiazepam for insomnia", 25:32, 1983 March 18 (Box 566, Folder 1350-1358)
- "STREPTOKINASE: Streptokinase for acute coronary artery thrombosis", 25:33 and Additional note on streptokinase, 25:44, 1983 April 1; 1983 April 29 (Box 567, Folder 1359-1364)
- "ACYCLOVIR: Intravenous ancyclovir (Zovirax)", 25:34, 1983 April 1 (Box 567, Folder 1365-1371)
- "IMMUNIZATION: Immunization and chemoprophylaxis for travelers", 25:37, 1983 April 15 (Box 568, Folder 1372-1377)
- "CHYMOPAPAIN: Chymopapain for herniated lumbar discs", 25:41, 1983 April 29 (Box 568, Folder 1378-1381, Box 569, Folder 1382-1383)
- "MEDICAL EQUIPMENT & DEVICES: Self-monitoring methods for blood glucose", 25:42 and Correction, 25:64, 1983 April 29; 1983 June 24 (Box 569, Folder 1384-1391)
- "PSYCHOPHARMACOLOGICAL AGENTS: Drugs for psychiatric disorders", 25:45, 1983 May 13 (Box 570, Folder 1392-1397, Box 571, Folder 1398-1403)
- "INSECT BITES AND STINGS: Insect venoms", 25:53, 1983 May 27 (Box 572, Folder 1404-1410)
- "TRANSPLANTATION: Organ donations for transplantation", 25:54, 1983 May 27 (Box 572, Folder 1411-1415)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Choice of cephalosporins", 25:57, 1983 June 10 (Box 573, Folder 1416-1422, Box 574, Folder 1423-1425)
- "BUMETANIDE: Bumetanide (Bumex) - a new "loop" diuretic", 25:61, 1983 June 24 (Box 574, Folder 1426-1430, Box 575, Folder 1431-1432)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY: Human insulin", 25:63, 1983 June 24 (Box 575, Folder 1433-1439)
- "NETILMICIN: Netilmicin sulfate (Netromycin)", 25:65, 1983 July 8 (Box 576, Folder 1440-1449)
- "SODIUM CELLULOSE PHOSPHATE: Sodium cellulose phosphate (Calcibind)", 25:67, 1983 July 8 (Box 577, Folder 1450-1458)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Oral contraceptives and the risk of cardiovascular disease", 25:69, 1983 July 22 (Box 578, Folder 1459-1466, Box 579, Folder 1467)
- "ETOMIDATE: Etomidate for induction of anesthesia", 25:71, 1983 July 22 (Box 579, Folder 1468-1474)
- "LIVER DISEASES: Branched-chain amino acids for the treatment of hepatic encephalopathy", 25:72, 1983 July 22 (Box 580, Folder 1475-1481)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction", 25:73, 1983 August 5 (Box 581, Folder 1482-1488)
- "CYCLOSPORINE: Cyclosporine - a new immunosuppressive agent", 25:77, 1983 August 19 (Box 582, Folder 1489-1497, Box 583, Folder 1498-1500)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES: A vaginal contraceptive sponge", 25:78, 1983 August 19 (Box 583, Folder 1501-1507)
- "NUTRITION & DIET (INFANTS): Whole cow's mild for older infants", 25:80, 1983 August 19 (Box 584, Folder 1508-1513)
- "DRUGS FOR EPILEPSY: Drugs for epilepsy", 25:81, 1983 September 2 (Box 584, Folder 1514-1519, Box 585, Folder 1520-1525)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE OVERDOSE): Diagnosis and management of acute drug abuse reactions", 25:85 and "Dosage of Naloxone", 25:108, 1983 September 16; 1983 November 25 (Box 586, Folder 1526-1532)
- "CROMOLYN SODIUM: Cromolyn sodium nasal spray for hay fever", 25:89, 1983 September 30 (Box 587, Folder 1533-1538)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1983-1984", 25:90, 1983 September 30 (Box 587, Folder 1539-1540, Box 588, Folder 1541-1544)
- "IMMUNIZATION: An expanded pneumococcal vaccine", 25:91, 1983 September 30 (Box 588, Folder 1545-1550)
- "BLOOD TRANSFUSION: Safe blood for transfusion", 25:93, 1983 October 14 (Box 588, Folder 1551, Box 589, Folder 1552-1556)
- "GUANADREL: Guanadrel (Hylorel) - a new antihypertensive drug", 25:95, 1983 October 14 (Box 589, Folder 1557-1561, Box 590, Folder 1562)
- "CORONARY ANGIOPLASTY: Percutaneous transluminal coronary angioplasty", 25:97, 1983 October 28 (Box 590, Folder 1563-1569)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: New topical antifungal drugs", 25:98, 1983 October 28 (Box 591, Folder 1570-1576)
- "GALL BLADDER: Chenodiol for dissolving gallstones", 25:101, 1983 November 11 (Box 591, Folder 1577, Box 592, Folder 1578-1584)
- "OTITIS MEDIA: Chemoprophylaxis for recurrent acute otitis media", 25:102, 1983 November 11 (Box 592, Folder 1585-1587, Box 593, Folder 1588-1589)
- "BANDAGES: Transparent wound bandages", 25:103, 1983 November 11 (Box 593, Folder 1590-1595, Box 594, Folder 1596-1601)
- "ISOTRETINOLIN: Update on isotretinolin (Accutane) for acne", 25:105, 1983 November 25 (Box 595, Folder 1602-1607)
- "GONADOTROPINS: Gonadorelin - synthetic LH-RH", 25:106, 1983 November 25 (Box 595, Folder 1608-1613, Box 596, Folder 1614-1615)
- "ANGIOGRAPHY: Intravenous digital subtraction angiography", 25:107, 1983 November 25 (Box 596, Folder 1616-1622)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftizoxine sodium (Cefizox)", 25:109, 1983 December 9 (Box 597, Folder 1623-1630)
- "ACETOHYDROXAMIC ACID: Oral acetohydroxamic acid (Lithostat) for- staghorn calculi", 25:110, 1983 December 9 (Box 598, Folder 1631-1637)
- "DIGITALIS: Digoxin solution in capsules (Lanoxicaps)", 25:111, 1983 December 9 (Box 598, Folder 1638-1640, Box 599, Folder 1641-1644)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for- surgery", 25:113, 1983 December 23 (Box 599, Folder 1645-1647, Box 600, Folder 1648-1654)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Handbook of Drug Interactions", 1983 (Box 601, Folder 1655-1661, Box 602, Folder 1662-1669)
- "THEOPHYLLINE: Sustained-release theophyllines", 26:1, 1984 January 6 (Box 603, Folder 1670-1677)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (ENDOCARDITIS): Prevention of bacterial endocarditis", 26:3, 1984 January 6 (Box 604, Folder 1678-1680)
- "SEXUALLY TRANSMITTED DISEASES: Treatment of sexually transmitted diseases", 26:5, 1984 January 20; 1984 February 3 (Box 604, Folder 1681-1684, Box 605, Folder 1685-1689)
- "DRUG INTERACTIONS: Drug Interactions update", 26:11, 1984 February 3; 1984 February 17 (Box 605, Folder 1690-1691)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Cefuroxime sodium (Zinacef)", 26:15, 1984 February 17 (Box 606, Folder 1692-1700)
- "INDAPAMIDE: Indapamide (Lozol) - a new antihypertensive agent and diuretic", 26:17, 1984 February 17 (Box 607, Folder 1701-1708)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: The choice of antimicrobial drugs", 26:19, 1984 March 2 (Box 608, Folder 1709-1715)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS: Drugs for parasitic infections", 26:27, 1984 March 16 (Box 609, Folder 1716-1722, Box 610, Folder 1723-1729, Box 611, Folder 1730-1731)
- "TRAZODONE: Priapism with trazodone (desyrel)", 26:35, 1984 March 30 (Box 611, Folder 1732-1736)
- "FUNGAL INFECTIONS: Drugs for treatment of systemic fungal infections", 26:36, 1984 March 30 (Box 611, Folder 1737-1739, Box 612, Folder 1740-1744)
- "FERTILIZATION: Invitro fertilization", 26:39, 1984 April 13 (Box 612, Folder 1745-1746, Box 613, Folder 1747-1750)
- "LEVOTHYROXINE: Potency of oral thyroxine preparations", 26:41, 1984 April 13 (Box 613, Folder 1751-1756)
- "HEMIN: Hemin infusion in acute intermittent porphyria", 26:42, 1984 April 13 (Box 613, Folder 1757-1758, Box 614, Folder 1759-1763)
- "SUCRALFATE: Sucralfate for peptic ulcer - a reappraisal" Consultants: ML Drafts, 26:43, 1984 May 25 (Box 614, Folder 1764-1769)
  Also includes - Correction: "Cost of Sucralfate Cimetidine and Ranitidine" 26:54, 1984 April 27
- "SMOKING: Nicotine gum", 26:47, 1984 May 11 (Box 615, Folder 1770-1775)
- "ETOPOSIDE: Etoposide (VP 16-213; VePesid)", 26:48, 1984 May 11 (Box 615, Folder 1776-1779, Box 616, Folder 1780-1781)
- "BENTIROMIED: Bentiromied - a test of pancreatic insufficiency", 26:50, 1984 May 11 (Box 616, Folder 1782-1788)
- "COCAINE: Adverse effects of cocaine abuse", 26:51, 1984 May 25 (Box 616, Folder 1789-1790, Box 617, Folder 1791-1796)
- "LASERS: Laser trabeculoplasty for open angle glaucoma", 26:52, 1984 May 25 (Box 617, Folder 1797-1799, Box 618, Folder 1800-1802)
- "ATRACURIUM: Atacurium", 26:53, 1984 May 25 (Box 618, Folder 1803-1809)
- "OBESITY: Phenylpropanolamine for weight reduction", 26:55, 1984 June 8 (Box 619, Folder 1810-1816, Box 620, Folder 1817-1818)
- "SUNBURN: Sunscreens", 26:55, 26:56, 1984 June 8 (Box 620, Folder 1819-1824)
- "NITROGLYCERIN: Nitroglycerin patches", 26:59, 1984 June 22 (Box 620, Folder 1825-1826, Box 621, Folder 1827-1833)
- "BETA-ADRENERGIC BLOCKERS: Beta-Adrenergic Blockers for anxiety", 26:61, 1984 June 22 (Box 621, Folder 1834-1837, Box 622, Folder 1838-1840)
- "IBUPROFEN: Ibuprofen without a prescription", 26:63, 1984 July 6 (Box 622, Folder 1841-1847)
- "SPORTS: Drugs in the Olympics", 26:65, 1984 July 6 (Box 623, Folder 1848-1852)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Mushroom poisoning", 26:67, 1984 July 20 (Box 623, Folder 1853-1856, Box 624, Folder 1857-1859)
- "EYE DISEASES: Laser therapy for age-related macular degeneration", 26:69, 1984 July 20 (Box 624, Folder 1860-1863, Box 625, Folder 1864-1865)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Cefonicid sodium (Monocid)", 26:71, 1984 August 3 (Box 625, Folder 1865-1870, Box 626, Folder 1871-1872)
- "VITAMINS: Toxic effects of vitamin overdosage", 26:73, 1984 August 3 (Box 626, Folder 1873-1879)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause psychiatric symptoms", 26:75 and Correction, 26:90, 1984 September 28; 1984 August (Box 627, Folder 1880-1885)
- "DIABETES THERAPY: Glyburide and glipizide", 26:79, 1984 August 31 (Box 627, Folder 1886-1889, Box 628, Folder 1890-1895, Box 629, Folder 1896-1899)
- "GROWTH HORMONE: Growth hormone", 26:80, 1984 August 31 (Box 629, Folder 1900-1902, Box 630, Folder 1903-1905)
- "DESMOPRESSIN: Desmopressin for hemophilia and other coagulation disorders", 26:82, 1984 August 31 (Box 630, Folder 1906-1909)
- "LABETALOL: Labetalol for hypertension", 26:83, 1984 September 14 (Box 631, Folder 1910-1916, Box 632, Folder 1917-1918)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1984-1985", 26:85, 1984 September 14 (Box 632, Folder 1919-1924, Box 633, Folder 1925)
- "ANAEROBIC INFECTIONS: Drugs for anaerobic infections", 26:87, 1984 September 28 (Box 633, Folder 1926-1931)
- "CANCER CHEMOTHERAPY: An implanted infusion pump for chemotherapy of- liver metastases", 26:89, 1984 September 28 (Box 634, Folder 1932-1938)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceforanide (Precef)", 26:91, 1984 October 12 (Box 634, Folder 1939-1941, Box 635, Folder 1942-1945)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Tri-Norinyl and Ortho-Novum 7/7/7 - two triphasic oral contraceptives", 26:93, 1984 October 12 (Box 635, Folder 1946-1951)
- "HEADACHE: Drugs for migraine", 26:95, 1984 October 26 (Box 636, Folder 1952-1956)
- "OBESITY: Suction lipectomy", 26:96, 1984 October 26 (Box 636, Folder 1957-1961)
- "METHYLPHENIDATE: Sustained released methylphenidate", 26:97, 1984 October 26 (Box 637, Folder 1962-1968)
- "SMOKING: Dental effects of nicotine gum", 26:98, 1984 October 26 (Box 637, Folder 1969-1973)
- "AMOXICILLIN-CLAVULANIC ACID: Amoxicillin-clavulanic acid (Augmentin)", 26:99, 1984 November 9 (Box 638, Folder 1974-1981)
- "MENSTRUATION DISORDERS: Progesterone for premenstrual syndrome", 26:101, 1984 November 9 (Box 639, Folder 1982-1988)
- "VECURONIUM: Vecuronium", 26:102, 1984 November 9 (Box 640, Folder 1989-1995)
- "PENTOXIFYLLINE: Pentoxifylline for intermittent claudication", 26:103, 1984 November 23 (Box 640, Folder 1996-2001, Box 641, Folder 2002-2003)
- "AMRINONE: Intravenous amrinone for congestive heart failure", 26:104, 1984 November 23 (Box 641, Folder 2004-2010)
- "SUFENTANIL: Sufentanin-a new opioid anesthetic", 26:106, 1984 November 23 (Box 642, Folder 2011-2017)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Drugs for hypertension", 26:107, 1984 December 7 (Box 643, Folder 2018-2024, Box 644, Folder 2025-2028)
- "OBESITY: Gastric operations for obesity", 26:113, 1984 December 21 (Box 644, Folder 2029-2031, Box 645, Folder 2032-2035)
- "VASODILATORS: Vasodilators for chronic congestive heart failure", 26:115, 1984 December 21 (Box 645, Folder 2035-2039, Box 646, Folder 2040-2043)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Handbook of antimicrobial therapy", Rev. ed., 1984 (Box 646, Folder 2044-2048, Box 647, Folder 2049-2058)
- "Nutrition and Diet: Diet and coronary heart disease", 27:1, 1985 January 4 (Box 648, Folder 2059-2063)
- "ERYTHROMYCIN: Oral erythromycins", 27:2, 1985 January 4 (Box 648, Folder 2064-2069, Box 649, Folder 2070-2071)
- "PIMOZIDE: Pimozide for tourette's disorder", 27:3, 1985 January 4 (Box 649, Folder 2072-2077)
- "CORTICOSTEROIDS: Corticosteroid aerosols for asthma", 27:5, 1985 January 18 (Box 650, Folder 2078-2086)
- "PENTAMIDINE: Pentamidine for pneumocystis carinii pneumonia", 27:6, 1985 January 18 (Box 651, Folder 2087-2091)
- "CROMOLYN SODIUM: Cromolyn sodium for allergic conjunctivitis", 27:7, 1985 January 18 (Box 651, Folder 2092-2097)
- "TOCAINIDE: Tocainide for arrhythmias", 27:9, 1985 February 1 (Box 651, Folder 2098, Box 652, Folder 2099-2105)
- "NALTREXONE: Naltrexone for opioid addiction", 27:11, 1985 February 1 (Box 652, Folder 2106-2108, Box 653, Folder 2109-2114)
- "CANCER CHEMOTHERAPY: Cancer Chemotherapy", 27:13, 1985 February 15 (Box 653, Folder 2115-2116, Box 654, Folder 2117-2124, Box 655, Folder 2125-2126)
- "METOCLOPRAMIDE: Metoclopramide (Reglan) for gastrointestinal reflux", 27:21, 1985 March 1 (Box 655, Folder 2127-2132)
- "HYPERTENSION THERAPY: Drugs for hypertensive emergencies", 27:22, 1985 March 1 (Box 655, Folder 2133-2137, Box 656, Folder 2138-2140)
- "RHEUMATISM AND ARTHRITIS (chemotherapy): Drugs for rheumatoid arthritis", 27:25, 1985 March 15 (Box 656, Folder 2141-2144, Box 657, Folder 2145-2151)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTING: Screening for AIDS", 27:29, 1985 March 29 (Box 658, Folder 2152-2156)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW (Amdinocillin): Amdinocillin", 27:30, 1985 March 29 (Box 658, Folder 2157-2164)
- "IMMUNIZATION: Immunizations and chemoprophylaxis for travelers", 27:33, 1985 April 12 (Box 659, Folder 2165-2172)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftriaxone sodium (Rocephin)", 27:37, 1985 April 26 (Box 660, Folder 2173-2181)
- "ELECTROLYTE LAVAGE SOLUTIONS: Oral electrolyte solutions for colonic lavage- before colonoscopy or barium enema", 27:39, 1985 April 26 (Box 661, Folder 2182-2187)
- "ACYCLOVIR: Oral acyclovir for genital herpes simplex infection", 27:41, 1985 May 10 (Box 661, Folder 2188-2192, Box 662, Folder 2193-2195)
- "NUCLEAR MAGNETIC RESONANCE: Magnetic resonance imaging", 27:43, 1985 May 10 (Box 662, Folder 2196-2201, Box 663, Folder 2202-2203)
- "HEPARIN: Dihydroergotamine - Heparin to prevent postoperative deep vein thrombosis", 27:45, 1985 May 24 (Box 663, Folder 2204-2210)
- "BILOLTEROL: Bitolterol - A new bronchodilator", 27:46, 1985 May 24 (Box 663, Folder 2211, Box 664, Folder 2212-2216)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, ORAL: Triphasil - a new oral contraceptive", 27:48, 1985 May 24 (Box 664, Folder 2217-2222)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Rapid office diagnostic tests for streptococcal pharyngitis", 27:49, 1985 June 7 (Box 664, Folder 2223, Box 665, Folder 2224-2228)
- "EAR: Cochlear Implants", 27:51, 1985 June 7 (Box 665, Folder 2229-2236)
- "OSTEOPOROSIS: Synthetic calcitonin for postmenopausal osteoporosis", 27:53, 1985 June 21 (Box 666, Folder 2237-2244)
- "ESTROGENS: Estrogens in cosmetics", 27:54, 1985 June 21 (Box 666, Folder 2245-2248)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Exertional heat injury", 27:55, 1985 June 21 (Box 666, Folder 2249, Box 667, Folder 2250-2253)
- "GROWTH HORMONE: Problems with growth hormone", 27:57, 1985 July 5 (Box 667, Folder 2254-2258)
- "ACEBUTOLOL: Acebutolol", 27:58, 1985 July 5 (Box 667, Folder 2259-2260, Box 668, Folder 2261-2267)
- "IMMUNIZATION: (Vaccines): Haemophilus influenza type b vaccine", 27:61, 1985 July 19 (Box 668, Folder 2268, Box 669, Folder 2269-2274)
- "INSECT REPELLENTS: Insect repellants", 27:62, 1985 July 19 (Box 669, Folder 2275-2280)
- "ANTIHISTAMINES: Terfenadine - a non-sedating antihistamine", 27:65, 1985 August 2 (Box 669, Folder 2281, Box 670, Folder 2282-2286)
- "VITAMINS: Vitamin supplements", 27:66, 1985 August 2 (Box 670, Folder 2287-2291, Box 671, Folder 2292-2294)
- "TICARCILLIN CLAVULANIC ACID: Ticarcillin-Clavulanic acid (Timentin)", 27:69, 1985 August 16 (Box 671, Folder 2295-2301, Box 672, Folder 2302-2304)
- "LEUPROLIDE: Leuprolide for prostate cancer", 27:71, 1985 August 16 (Box 672, Folder 2305-2310)
- "EXTRACORPOREAL SHOCK WAVE LITHOTRIPSY (ESWL): Extracorporeal shock wave lithotripsy (ESWL) for urinary tract stones", 27:72, 1985 August 16 (Box 673, Folder 2311-2314)
- "NOMIFENSINE: Nomifensine (Merital), a new non-tricyclic antidepressant", 27:73, 1985 August 30 (Box 673, Folder 2315-2320, Box 674, Folder 2321-2322)
- "LIPIDS, DRUG REDUCTION: Lipid - Lowering drugs", 27:74, 1985 August 30 (Box 674, Folder 2323-2328, Box 675, Folder 2329-2332)
- "ADDICTION (Abuse-Overdose): Acute drug abuse reactions", 27:77, 1985 September 13 (Box 675, Folder 2333-2335, Box 676, Folder 2336-2342)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1985-1986", 27:81, 1985 September 27 (Box 676, Folder 2343-2344, Box 677, Folder 2345-2347)
- "OVALATION INDUCTION: Drugs that induce ovulation", 27:82, 1985 September 27 (Box 677, Folder 2348-2354, Box 678, Folder 2355-2356)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Ceftazidime (Fortaz)", 27:85, 1985 October 11 (Box 678, Folder 2357-2362, Box 679, Folder 2363-2365)
- "TRILOSTANE: Trilostane for cushing's syndrome", 27:87, 1985 October 11 (Box 679, Folder 2366-2371)
- "GOLD AURANOFIN (Ridaura)", 27:89, 1985 October 25 (Box 679, Folder 2372-2374, Box 680, Folder 2375-2379)
- "OSTEOPOROSIS: Estrogen plus a progestin for prevention of postmenopausal osteoporosis", 27:91, 1985 October 25 (Box 680, Folder 2380-2381, Box 681, Folder 2382-2384)
- "ANALGESICS: Introspinal morphine for postoperative analgesia", 27:92, 1985 October 25 (Box 681, Folder 2385-2390)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: Safety of antimicrobial drugs in pregnancy", 27:93, 1985 November 8 (Box 682, Folder 2391-2397)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Transdermal clonidine for hypertension", 27:95, 1985 November 8 (Box 682, Folder 2398, Box 683, Folder 2399-2403)
- "MARIJUANA: Synthetic marijuana for nausea and vomiting due to cancer chemotherapy", 27:97, 1985 November 22 (Box 683, Folder 2404-2410)
- "IMMUNIZATION: Routine immunization for adults", 27:98, 1985 November 22 (Box 683, Folder 2411, Box 684, Folder 2412-2416)
- "GROWTH HORMONE: Biosynthetic growth hormone", 27:101, 1985 December 6 (Box 684, Folder 2417-2421)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Office test for serum theophylline", 27:102, 1985 December 6 (Box 685, Folder 2422-2428)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Captopril for mild to moderate hypertension", 27:103, 1985 December 6 (Box 685, Folder 2429-2433, Box 686, Folder 2434-2435)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE(Surgery): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for- surgery", 27:105, 1985 December 20 (Box 686, Folder 2436-2441, Box 687, Folder 2442)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Asthma, Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2443-2444)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Epilepsy, Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2445)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Original Manuscript, Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2446)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Psychiatric drugs, Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 687, Folder 2447-2448)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Arrhythmias, Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2449-2451)
- "MEDICAL LETTER (SPECIAL PUBLICATIONS): Drugs of choice from- The Medical Letter" Back up, Rv. Ed., 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2452)
- "ERYTHROMYCIN: Additional Note", not published, 1985 (Box 688, Folder 2453-2456)